<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>TVCeleb.com - The Living Archive of TV Fandom</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com</link>
<description>The world&#x27;s largest repository of TV character fan sites, fan social media &amp; aggregated content. Explore characters, fan communities, and ecosystems across every TV show.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<atom:link href="https://tvceleb.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<image>
<url>https://tvceleb.com/favicon.ico</url>
<title>TVCeleb.com</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com</link>
</image>
<item>
<title>Grogu / Baby Yoda - The Mandalorian</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/grogu/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/grogu/</guid>
<description>Grogu — universally known as Baby Yoda before his name was revealed — is a fifty-year-old infant of the same mysterious species as Jedi Master Yoda. Despite his age, Grogu is developmentally equivalent to a toddler, a fact that provides both endless charm and genuine narrative stakes. He is the asse...</description>
<category>The Mandalorian</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Walter White - Breaking Bad</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/walter-white/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/walter-white/</guid>
<description>Walter White begins as an overqualified, underpaid high school chemistry teacher in Albuquerque, New Mexico. When diagnosed with inoperable lung cancer, he makes a fateful decision to use his chemistry expertise to manufacture methamphetamine, partnering with former student Jesse Pinkman.  As Walter...</description>
<category>Breaking Bad</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tony Soprano - The Sopranos</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/tony-soprano/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/tony-soprano/</guid>
<description>Tony Soprano is the boss of the DiMeo crime family in New Jersey, a man of enormous appetite and contradictions who revolutionized television drama. He is simultaneously a loving father who dotes on the ducks in his swimming pool and a ruthless mob boss capable of strangling an informant with his ba...</description>
<category>The Sopranos</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jon Snow - Game of Thrones</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/jon-snow/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/jon-snow/</guid>
<description>Jon Snow begins as the illegitimate son of Ned Stark, raised at Winterfell but always aware of his outsider status. Seeking purpose and honor, he joins the Night&#x27;s Watch at the Wall, where he rises through the ranks from steward to Lord Commander. His early experiences beyond the Wall — confronting ...</description>
<category>Game of Thrones</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Thomas Shelby - Peaky Blinders</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/thomas-shelby/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/thomas-shelby/</guid>
<description>Thomas &quot;Tommy&quot; Shelby returns from the trenches of World War I a changed man — haunted by his experiences in France, addicted to opium, and possessed by a ruthless ambition that will transform him from a Birmingham street gang leader into one of the most powerful men in England. As the head of the S...</description>
<category>Peaky Blinders</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Daemon Targaryen - House of the Dragon</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/daemon-targaryen/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/daemon-targaryen/</guid>
<description>Daemon Targaryen is the younger brother of King Viserys I and the most dangerous member of House Targaryen. A peerless warrior and dragonrider of the fearsome Caraxes, Daemon is charismatic, ambitious, and deeply volatile. He craves recognition and power but chafes under his brother&#x27;s reign, feeling...</description>
<category>House of the Dragon</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Eleven / Jane Hopper - Stranger Things</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/eleven-jane-hopper/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/eleven-jane-hopper/</guid>
<description>Eleven, born Jane Ives and later known as Jane Hopper, is a girl with extraordinary psychokinetic and telepathic abilities developed through experimental testing at Hawkins National Laboratory under the supervision of Dr. Martin Brenner, whom she was forced to call &quot;Papa.&quot; Raised in near-total isola...</description>
<category>Stranger Things</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rue Bennett - Euphoria</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/rue-bennett/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/rue-bennett/</guid>
<description>Rue Bennett is the unreliable narrator and emotional center of Euphoria, a seventeen-year-old struggling with drug addiction following the death of her father. Fresh out of rehab as the series begins, Rue has no real intention of staying clean — she views sobriety as something other people want for ...</description>
<category>Euphoria</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rhaenyra Targaryen - House of the Dragon</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/rhaenyra-targaryen/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/rhaenyra-targaryen/</guid>
<description>Rhaenyra Targaryen is the firstborn child of King Viserys I Targaryen and was named his heir to the Iron Throne, making her the first woman ever designated to rule the Seven Kingdoms. Her claim is challenged from the moment of her naming, as the lords of Westeros harbor deep reservations about a rul...</description>
<category>House of the Dragon</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Homelander - The Boys</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/homelander/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/homelander/</guid>
<description>Homelander is the leader of The Seven, Vought International&#x27;s premier superhero team, and the most powerful being on the planet. To the public, he is America&#x27;s golden boy — a patriotic, cape-wearing symbol of hope modeled on Superman. Behind the facade, he is a profoundly damaged, narcissistic socio...</description>
<category>The Boys</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jinx / Powder - Arcane</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/jinx/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/jinx/</guid>
<description>Powder is a bright, inventive young girl from the undercity of Zaun, the younger sister of Vi and the adopted daughter of Vander. After a catastrophic failed heist leads to Vander&#x27;s death and Vi&#x27;s imprisonment, Powder is abandoned — her sister&#x27;s last words to her being &quot;You&#x27;re a jinx.&quot; This rejectio...</description>
<category>Arcane</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jesse Pinkman - Breaking Bad</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/jesse-pinkman/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/jesse-pinkman/</guid>
<description>Jesse Pinkman starts as a small-time methamphetamine cook and dealer, a former student of Walter White who becomes his unlikely partner in crime. Initially portrayed as a reckless slacker, Jesse reveals surprising depth and moral complexity as the series progresses.  Unlike Walter, who embraces the ...</description>
<category>Breaking Bad</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Daenerys Targaryen - Game of Thrones</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/daenerys-targaryen/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/daenerys-targaryen/</guid>
<description>Daenerys Targaryen begins as a timid, abused young woman sold into marriage to Dothraki warlord Khal Drogo by her brother Viserys. Through sheer will and resilience, she transforms from a frightened girl into the &quot;Mother of Dragons,&quot; hatching three dragon eggs in Drogo&#x27;s funeral pyre and emerging un...</description>
<category>Game of Thrones</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Michael Scott - The Office (US)</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/michael-scott/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/michael-scott/</guid>
<description>Michael Scott is the regional manager of Dunder Mifflin&#x27;s Scranton branch, a man whose desperate need to be loved by everyone around him drives both the comedy and the heart of the show. His management style is a chaotic blend of inappropriate jokes, misguided motivational speeches, and occasional f...</description>
<category>The Office (US)</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Chandler Bing - Friends</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/chandler-bing/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/chandler-bing/</guid>
<description>Chandler Bing is the sarcastic, self-deprecating heart of Friends — a man who uses humor as armor against a deeply painful childhood. The son of a Las Vegas drag queen father and an erotic novelist mother whose very public divorce scarred him, Chandler deflects emotional intimacy with rapid-fire jok...</description>
<category>Friends</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Din Djarin / The Mandalorian - The Mandalorian</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/din-djarin/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/din-djarin/</guid>
<description>Din Djarin is a lone bounty hunter operating in the lawless outer reaches of the galaxy, a foundling rescued as a child by the Mandalorian warrior sect known as the Children of the Watch. Raised in their strict creed — which forbids removing his helmet in front of any living being — Din has built hi...</description>
<category>The Mandalorian</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tanya McQuoid - The White Lotus</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/tanya-mcquoid/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/tanya-mcquoid/</guid>
<description>Tanya McQuoid is a wealthy, emotionally fragile woman who arrives at the White Lotus resort in Hawaii carrying her recently deceased mother&#x27;s ashes and a lifetime of unresolved trauma. Tanya is simultaneously sympathetic and exasperating — generous but oblivious, desperate for connection but incapab...</description>
<category>The White Lotus</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jimmy McGill / Saul Goodman - Better Call Saul</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/jimmy-mcgill/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/jimmy-mcgill/</guid>
<description>Jimmy McGill begins as a small-time con artist turned public defender, desperate to earn the respect of his brilliant older brother Chuck and the legal establishment that views him as &quot;Slippin&#x27; Jimmy.&quot; Working out of the back room of a nail salon, Jimmy possesses genuine legal talent and a gift for ...</description>
<category>Better Call Saul</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Daryl Dixon - The Walking Dead</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/daryl-dixon/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/daryl-dixon/</guid>
<description>Daryl Dixon begins the series as an angry, volatile redneck living in the shadow of his abusive, racist older brother Merle. Originally conceived as a minor character, Daryl&#x27;s journey from outsider to indispensable leader became the emotional backbone of The Walking Dead, driven by Norman Reedus&#x27;s m...</description>
<category>The Walking Dead</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loki Laufeyson - Loki</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/loki-laufeyson/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/loki-laufeyson/</guid>
<description>The Loki of this series is not the one who experienced years of growth and ultimately sacrificed himself in Avengers: Infinity War — this is the 2012 variant who escaped with the Tesseract during the Avengers&#x27; time heist in Endgame, still arrogant, still scheming, and still convinced of his own glor...</description>
<category>Loki</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tyrion Lannister - Game of Thrones</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/tyrion-lannister/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/tyrion-lannister/</guid>
<description>Tyrion Lannister is the youngest son of Tywin Lannister, head of the wealthiest family in Westeros. Born a dwarf, Tyrion has been despised by his father and sister Cersei his entire life. He compensates for his physical stature with a razor-sharp intellect, cutting wit, and a voracious appetite for ...</description>
<category>Game of Thrones</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wednesday Addams - Wednesday</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/wednesday-addams/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/wednesday-addams/</guid>
<description>Wednesday Addams arrives at Nevermore Academy, a school for supernatural outcasts, after being expelled from multiple normal schools. Cold, brilliant, and unapologetically morbid, she initially views Nevermore as just another institution to endure. But when a series of murders rock the school and th...</description>
<category>Wednesday</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Joel Miller - The Last of Us</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/joel-miller/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/joel-miller/</guid>
<description>Joel Miller is a hardened survivor in a post-apocalyptic America ravaged by the Cordyceps fungal pandemic. Twenty years before the story begins, Joel lost his teenage daughter Sarah in the chaos of outbreak night — shot by a panicked soldier — and this primal wound has defined every choice he has ma...</description>
<category>The Last of Us</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ted Lasso - Ted Lasso</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/ted-lasso-character/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/ted-lasso-character/</guid>
<description>Ted Lasso is an American college football coach hired to manage AFC Richmond, an English Premier League soccer team, despite having no experience with the sport. Initially brought in by team owner Rebecca Welton as a sabotage strategy to ruin the club, Ted&#x27;s relentless optimism, folksy wisdom, and g...</description>
<category>Ted Lasso</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Beth Dutton - Yellowstone</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/beth-dutton/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/beth-dutton/</guid>
<description>Beth Dutton is the fiercely loyal and devastatingly sharp-tongued daughter of John Dutton. A brilliant financier with a talent for corporate warfare, Beth wields her intelligence like a weapon, dismantling her family&#x27;s enemies with the same ferocity she uses to guard her emotional wounds. She is, by...</description>
<category>Yellowstone</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aemond Targaryen - House of the Dragon</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/aemond-targaryen/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/aemond-targaryen/</guid>
<description>Aemond Targaryen is the second son of King Viserys I and Queen Alicent, a prince forged by resentment and ambition. As a child, he was mocked for being the only Targaryen of his generation without a dragon, a humiliation that drove him to claim the fearsome Vhagar — the largest living dragon — at a ...</description>
<category>House of the Dragon</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fleabag - Fleabag</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/fleabag/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/fleabag/</guid>
<description>Fleabag is a dry-witted, sexually frank young woman navigating life in London after a series of devastating personal losses. She runs a struggling guinea pig-themed cafe left to her by her late best friend Boo, whose death — which Fleabag played a direct role in — haunts her throughout the series. S...</description>
<category>Fleabag</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rust Cohle - True Detective</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/rust-cohle/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/rust-cohle/</guid>
<description>Rustin &quot;Rust&quot; Cohle is a Louisiana State Police homicide detective whose philosophical worldview and haunted past make him one of television&#x27;s most complex protagonists. A former undercover narcotics agent in Texas, Cohle suffered a devastating personal tragedy — the death of his young daughter — th...</description>
<category>True Detective</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rick Grimes - The Walking Dead</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/rick-grimes/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/rick-grimes/</guid>
<description>Rick Grimes is a small-town sheriff&#x27;s deputy from King County, Georgia, who awakens from a coma to find the world has been overtaken by the undead. His desperate search for his wife Lori and son Carl leads him to a group of survivors outside Atlanta, where he quickly assumes the role of leader throu...</description>
<category>The Walking Dead</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Negan - The Walking Dead</title>
<link>https://tvceleb.com/characters/negan/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://tvceleb.com/characters/negan/</guid>
<description>Negan is the charismatic, leather-jacket-wearing leader of the Saviors, a brutal authoritarian community that extorts other groups for supplies through violence and intimidation. His weapon of choice, a barbed-wire-wrapped baseball bat named Lucille (after his deceased wife), becomes one of televisi...</description>
<category>The Walking Dead</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>